Hello friends, welcome to our
channel Stock Market Investors. I hope
you will join us. So
friends, the person talking here is ICICI
Lombard General Insurance. We have presented our quarterly
numbers. This is an ICICI Bank
company and a general insurance company.
Today, you can
see the numbers through the numbers page.
First of all, you will see the difference.
Friends, the face value of ₹5 equity
shares is 10 rupees. It is up to 50%.
You will see the difference.
When will you get it? What will you get? It will be
updated in the coming time. There is no update right now. It will
only be updated in the meeting in the office. Right now, a
dividend of Rs 5 has been announced. It will be given to you. ₹5
difference. It will be given to you. Only then will you
see the result of the company. So, here, all the
digits will be seen in Hussain NAC and
here, I am talking about the result. So, let me
zoom in a little bit so
that you get a proper fit in the skin.
You will see how Shravan is doing.
Friends, here in the last  Quarter difference
means quarter phone number of last year's
quarter phone number of current year's quarter,
exact numbers of current year, you will get to see them
here, so here let's talk about total income,
how much income the company is generating from its business, so
look at the total income here, the phone is a little small, no problem, let
me tell you, what the company was generating here last year was
348706 kund 40 lakhs, which is four
lakh 63 thousand 624 lakhs, it means that the company is
showing early growth, it is a very good source,
talking about quarters, 334004 1471
quarterly, a little increase is visible in the company here, it is
not much, but it
looks very good, a gallery, quite early, the
company is generating good revenue in both,
but is the
company's expense big, should they see
that it should not be expressed strongly,
so here you will get to see the expense,
how much is the total expense of the company,
last year two lakhs, 51 lakhs from Doctor Saheb
and Jyotishwar
368648  If we talk about the last quarter, then
3 lakh 58 thousand one hundred
people means doctors in the quarter and this yagya has
increased a lot in expenses,
chopped tomatoes, the company expenses are a little high, no problem, we have to
see the profit,
what is the profit of the company,
we will see that in the last, if we talk about profit after tax, then I will
force you to do it here so that
you can see proper visibility here,
here you will get to see
how are the company results, last year the company earned
34567 lakhs which is an amount
of 3251, for us, we will see a drop here, the company's
profit revenue is increasing, if the
company's quarter was
1753 lakhs and the Italian company a little,
friends, I told you that the company has a lot of revenue
here in the company, it generates good revenue,
but due to the increase in the company's earnings, the
company is seen going into the launch,
5 different segments have been seen,
if we talk about the
company's EBITDA in net premium, a
little bit is visible for this, the
investment the company makes from that  If we talk about it, then the
company had to be closed a little bit, so
come friends, the company is good, it is doing a little bit, if you
see a decline in this company with the insurance company, then you can
definitely fold it a little bit and leave it, the
company is not bad because it will
spend the company's time, if the company starts making profit then we
can do it,
okay, I will
talk to you later, if you liked the video then like,
subscribe and keep subscribing to the channel,
bye-bye take care till Yagnik